#### Contact

7th Avenue, Gaur City - 1, Noida Extension Sector 4, UP-201301 8376877308 (Home) giridharraut98@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/giridhar-rautb328271a9 (LinkedIn) github.com/giridat/note-wise (Portfolio)

#### Top Skills

Dart

Android Studio

Flutter

# Giridhar Raut

Software Testing | Android App development | Delhi, India

#### Summary

Programming languages:

- 1. Dart 4/5 (good knowledge of OOPS)
- 2. Python 3/5
- 3. XML 2/5
- 4. Javascript 2/5

Can handle translation of UI designs comfortably.

Flutter knowledge:

- 1. go\_router package (routes)
- 2. MVI architecture
- 3. Provider state management
- 4. Flexible UI designing
- 5. Firebase backend
- 6. Figma
- 7. Can setup CI/CD pipeline using GitHub actions
- looking forward to immediate opportunities in app development sector.
- Ample knowledge of working with GitHub, Autolt, Slack, Jira etc.

An experienced Manual Tester in Games, websites and Mobile apps testing.

Volunteer Tester for multiple 3rd party Microsoft Flight Simulator 2020 developers developing study level Aircrafts. Developing basic Java and JavaScript knowledge along with understanding XML and HTML by working on Flight Sim aircrafts.

A Bachelor of Computer Applications from Guru Gobind Singh Indraprastha University.

Pursuing Masters of Computer Applications as a Distance learning program from Chandigarh University.

Staying connected with the knowledgeable world or any sort of knowledge gaining platform to stay motivated towards achieving my goals.

## Experience

Keywords Studios Quality Assurance Tester February 2021 - Present (1 year 7 months) Gurugram, Haryana, India

Manual Testing/ Automation Testing

National Institute of Indian Classical Dance Website Manager January 2021 - April 2021 (4 months) New Delhi, Delhi, India

Giridhar Trading Company
Ecommerce Manager
August 2020 - January 2021 (6 months)
Delhi, India

### Education

#### CHANDIGARH UNIVERSITY

Master of Computer Applications - MCA, Computer Programming, Specific Applications · (November 2021 - November 2023)

Guru Gobind Singh Indraprastha University

Bachelor of Computer Applications - BCA , Computer Programming, Specific Applications · (May 2017 - February 2020)

**Brillica Services** 

High School Diploma, Data Science (2020 - 2020)

Integrated Institute of Technology

Bachelor of Computer Applications , Computer/Information Technology · (2017 - 2020)

Vandana International School - India Senior Secondary · (2014 - 2017)